Guide to the Livingston Farrand papers, 1921-1939.
Farrand, Livingston Papers
- PAN-PAP Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  Papish, Jacob. Dept. of Chemistry.
- Papish, Jacob., 1925-36 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- PAR-Park Miscellaneous., 1921-28 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  University of Paris.
- Park-Parker., 1926-36 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  Parker, James W.
- Parker-PARM Miscellaneous., 1919-34 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Parmelee Miscellaneous., 1930-34 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  Parmelee, Alice Maury.
- PARM-PARR Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  Parran, Thomas. New York State Dept. of Health.
- PARR-PAS Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  Parran, Thomas; Parsons, Samuel. New York State Dept. of Health.
- PAS-PATT Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  Passmore, Lincoln K.; Pasteur, Louis.
- Patterson, Woodford., 1928-36 (Box 27, Folder 24-38)
  Secretary of the University.
- PATT-PEA Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- PEA-Peace Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  National Peace Conference.
- Peace-PEAR Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  Pearson, Arthur; Pearson, E. J.
- PEAR-Pease Miscellaneous., 1921-33 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  Pearson, Frank A.; Pearson, R. A. University of Maryland.
- Pease-PEI Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  Peaslee, Horace W.; Peer, Sherman.
- PEI-PEN Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- PENN Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 27, Folder 45-46)
  Penney, Mark E.; Gates, Thomas S. University of Pennsylvania; Pennsylvania State College.
- PENN-PENS Miscellaneous. White, J. DuPratt. Pension Fund Committee., 1922-35 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- Pensions., 1926-37 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Pensions-PER Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- PERK-PERR Miscellaneous., 1926-34 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  Perkins, Frances; Perla, Jacob.
- PERR-PERS Miscellaneous., 1927-33 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  Perry, Lewis; Pershing, John J.
- PERS-PET Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  Pertsch, John G.; Peterson, Abbott.
- PET Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  Petry, Loren C. Summer Session.
- PET-PEY Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- PF-PH Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Pfann, George R.
- PH-PHI Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  Phelps, A. C. Phi Beta Kappa.
- PHI B-K Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  Phi Delta Theta.
- PHI K-PHIL Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- PHIL-PHILL Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- PHILL Miscellaneous., 1928-31 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  Phillips, E. F.
- PHILL-PHIP Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  Perry, Lewis; Bradford, Eugene F. Office of Admissions.
- PHIP-PIE Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- PIE-PIL Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  Pietsch, Walter G.; Pigman, Augustus.
- PIL-PITT Miscellaneous., 1929-35 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  Pinchot, Gifford.
- PITT Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- PITZ-PIZZ Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  Piwkowski, Thomas R.
- PLA-PLAG Miscellaneous., 1921-37 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  Place, Ira A.
- PLAG-Play Miscellaneous., 1928-34 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  Playgrounds.
- Play-PLU Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Placement., 1928-37 (Box 28, Folder 16-18)
  Williams, H. H.
- Plan Commission., 1922-26 (Box 28, Folder 19-21)
- POD-POL Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- POL-POP Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  Pope, Paul R.
- POP-PORT Miscellaneous., 1926-34 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- POST-Postal Miscellaneous., 1925 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Postal Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 28, Folder 26-27)
  Postal day letters and postal telegrams.
- POT-POTT Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  Potter, Lloyd G.
- POTT-POU Miscellaneous., 1930-36 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  Pound, Cuthbert W.
- POU Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 28, Folder 30-31)
  Pound, Cuthbert W.; Pound, Roscoe.
- POU-POW Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  Pound, Roscoe.
- POW Miscellaneous., 1931-34 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  Powers, William H.
- PRA-PRES Miscellaneous., 1924-31 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- PRES-PRI Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  Hopkins, Ernest M. Committee to Consider the Selection of a President.
- PRI-PRIN Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  Smith, Datus C. Princeton University.
- Princeton University., 1924-35 (Box 28, Folder 37-39)
  Dodds, Harold W.; Hibben, John G.
- PRIN-PRIZ Miscellaneous., 1926-34 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Prizes Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- PRO-Proctor Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  Mead, Charles G.
- Proctor-PROG Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  Twesten, Theodore H.; Duffey, John T.; Smith, Avery D.
- Prohibition., 1932-36 (Box 28, Folder 44-46)
  Women's Organization for National Prohibition Reform.
- PRO-PRY Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- PSI-PSY Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  Psi Upsilon.
- PSY-PU Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  Dept. of Psychology; New York State Dept. of Health.
- Public Miscellaneous., 1921-27 (Box 28, Folder 50-51)
  Stutz, Harry G.; Moree, Edward A.; Adams, Bristow; Muchmore, G. B.
- Public-Publishing., 1922-35 (Box 28, Folder 52)
- Publishing Report., 1935 (Box 28, Folder 53)
- Publishing., 1935 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  Birk, Louis P.
- New York State Public Health Council., 1932-35 (Box 28, Folder 55-57)
  Parran, Thomas; Godfrey, Edward S. New York State Dept. of Health.
- New York State Public Health Council., 1932-37 (Box 29, Folder 1-16)
  Godfrey, Edward S.; Parran, Thomas.; New York State Dept. of Health.
- PUC-PUMP Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  Vizcarrondo, Francisco.
- PUMP-PUR Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  Pumpelly, Laurence. Dept. of Romance Languages and Literatures.
- PUR-PURD Miscellaneous., 1924-32 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  Purdue University.
- PUSH-PYR Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  Pyrke, Berne A. New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets.
- PYR-PYTH Miscellaneous., 1924-31 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Q-QU Miscellaneous., 1921-30 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  Quarles, James T.
- QU-RAD Miscellaneous., 1923-31 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  Quill Club; Radcliffe College.
- RAB-RAD Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  Rabotnikoff, A. S.; Rahn, Otto. Race Betterment Conference.
- RAIL-RAMM Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  Rammelkamp, C. H. Illinois College.
- RAMM-RAND Miscellaneous., 1923-29 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  Rammelkamp, C. H.; Ford, Henry; Randall, Fred M. Illinois College.
- RAND-RANS Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  Ransom, William L.
- RANS-RAV Miscellaneous., 1921-31 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  Ranum, Arthur; Powley, Randle H.; Garrett, Robert T.; Rappenecker, Caspar.
- RAV-RAYT Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  Ravenel, W. deC. University of Nanking.
- Radio., 1927-37 (Box 29, Folder 30-43)
  Tyson, Levering; Garland, Hamlin; Sanderson, E. N.; Lincoln, Paul M. National Broadcasting Company; National Committee on Education by Radio; Radio Broadcasting Committee.
- Radio Broadcasting., 1931-36 (Box 29, Folder 44-46)
  Mann, Albert R.; Tyson, Levering; Gannett, Frank E.; Lincoln, Paul M. National Committee on Education by Radio.
- REA-REAL Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- REAL-RECK Miscellaneous., 1921-33 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  Recknagel, A. B. Institute of Forestry (proposed).
- RECK-RED Miscellaneous. Recknagel, A. B. Institute of Forestry (proposed); Reconstruction Home (Ithaca, N. Y. )., 1923-34 (Box 29, Folder 49)
- RED Miscellaneous., 1921-32 (Box 29, Folder 50-51)
  Reddick, Donald; Mann, Albert R.; Redfield, Casper L. Cleanliness Institute; United States Dept. of Agriculture.
- Reed Miscellaneous., 1928-35 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  Reed, Harold L.; Reed, Daniel A.
- Reed, Harold L., 1922-29 (Box 29, Folder 53)
- Reed, H. D., 1921-37 (Box 29, Folder 54-55)
  Zoological Laboratory.
- Reed, H. D. - REEV Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  Reed College.
- REG-REI Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  Loomis, Milton E. Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York.
- REI Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 29, Folder 58-60)
  Reighard, Jacob; Reigart, John F.; Reiland, Karl.
- REI-REL Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 29, Folder 61)
- REM-REN Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  Renaud, E. B.; Ricketts, Palmer C. Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute.
- REN-RES Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  Requardt, Gustav J.
- RES Miscellaneous., 1929-37 (Box 30, Folder 3-5)
  Research Corporation; ROTC; ROTC Association of the United States.
- RES-RET Miscellaneous., 1930-35 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  ROTC Association of the United States.
- RET-REX Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Rhees Miscellaneous., 1923-32 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  Rhees, Rush. University of Rochester.
- Rhees-RHO Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  Rhees, Rush; Rhodes, Fred H.
- RHO-Rhodes Scholarship Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  Patterson, Woodford.
- Rhodes Scholarship., 1921-30 (Box 30, Folder 11-12)
- RIA-Rice Miscellaneous., 1927-35 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  Rice, Edward A.; Rice, James E. Rice Institute.
- Rice Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  Rice, James E.; Rice, William Gorham (Mrs, Harriet Langdon). Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
- Rice-RICH Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  Rich, Stephen G.; Needham, James G.; Richmond, C. A. Union College.
- RICH-Richt Miscellaneous., 1923-29 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  Richmond, C. A.; Adams, Bristow. Union College.
- Richtmyer, F. K., 1932-37 (Box 30, Folder 17-27)
  Graduate School; International Association; Carnegie Corporation; Heckscher Research Council; Ward Fund; Institute for the Study of Radiation (proposed).
- RIC Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  Rickard, Edgar; Ricketts, Palmer C. Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute.
- RIDD-RIE Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  Riegelman, Harold; Ries, Heinrich. Riding Hall.
- Ries, Heinrich. Dept. of Geology., 1922-36 (Box 30, Folder 30-32)
- Ries-RIPP Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- RIS-ROB Miscellaneous., 1924-32 (Box 30, Folder 34-35)
- ROB Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 30, Folder 36-40)
  Roberts, Isaac P.; Robinson, G. H.; Robinson, James R.; Robinson, Nelson.
- ROC-ROS Miscellaneous., 1930-33 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Rochester., 1922-37 (Box 30, Folder 42-45)
  Valentine, Alan; Rhees, Rush. University of Rochester.
- Rockefeller Foundation., 1934-37 (Box 30, Folder 46-48)
  Gregg, Alan; Rockefeller, John D.
- ROC-ROE Miscellaneous., 1926-35 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  Rockefeller, John D.; Rockwell, George H.; Rodd, Rennell.
- ROE-ROW Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  Horch, Louis L.; Palmer, Archie M. Roerich Museum.
- Rogalsky, George F., 1931-37 (Box 30, Folder 51-59)
  Office of the Treasurer.
- Rogalsky, George F., 1927-33 (Box 31, Folder 1-6)
- ROG-ROL Miscellaneous., 1922-27 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  Rollins, Philip Ashton.
- ROLL-ROM Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  Holt, Hamilton. Rollins College.
- ROM-RON Miscellaneous., 1929-36 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  Beecher, Beatrice B.; Olds, Robert E.; Romell, Lars G.
- RON-ROOS Miscellaneous., 1916-36 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  Hosmer, Ralph S.; Roof, Clarence M.; Roosevelt, Theodore.
- Roosevelt Miscellaneous., 1931-36 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  Roosevelt, Eleanor; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Roosevelt, Theodore. Porto Rico.
- Roosevelt-ROV Miscellaneous., 1921-30 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  Roosevelt, Theodore.
- ROS-Rose Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  Rose, Flora. New York State College of Home Economics.
- Rose, Flora., 1923-34 (Box 31, Folder 14-16)
  New York State College of Home Economics.
- Rose Miscellaneous., 1925-28 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  Rose, Wickliffe.
- Rosenau-Ross Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  Rosenwald, Julius.
- Ross Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  Ross, Herbert W.
- Ross-ROSSI Miscellaneous., 1923-31 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  Ross, Howard S.; Rossiter, William G.
- ROSSI-ROT Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  Notestein, Wallace.
- ROT-ROU Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  Marie, the Queen of Roumania.
- ROW-ROY Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  Rowe, L. S. Royal Sanitary Institute.
- ROY-RUF Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  Keppel, David.
- RUG-RUR Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- RUR Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  Rushmore, David B. Institute for Rural Religious Training (proposed).
- RUSS Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 31, Folder 27-29)
  Russell Sage Foundation; Russian Student Fund.
- RUSS-RUT Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  Burmistroff, V. G. Russian Student Fund; Rutgers University.
- RUT-RY Miscellaneous., 1925-33 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  Rutgers University.
- ROTC: Military Training., 1931-32 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- ROTC: Military Training., 1931 (Box 31, Folder 33-34)
- ROTC: Military Training., 1926-27 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- ROTC: Compulsory Military Training-Petition., 1939 (Box 31, Folder 36-37)
- ROTC: Military Training., 1931 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- ROTC: Tropical Medicine., 1926-28 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- ROTC: Todd Professorship., 1928-29 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- ROTC: C. U. Athletic Assoc., 1931 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- ROTC: Radio., 1931-32 (Box 31, Folder 42-43)
- ROTC: Forestry Education., 1932 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- ROTC: Military Training., 1932 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- ROTC: Military Training., 1933 (Box 31, Folder 46-47)
- ROTC: Radio., 1933-34 (Box 31, Folder 48-49)
- ROTC: Forestry Education., 1932 (Box 31, Folder 50)
- ROTC: Radio., 1927-34 (Box 31, Folder 51-53)
- ROTC: Science Project., 1927 (Box 31, Folder 54)
- ROTC: Science Project., 1928 (Box 31, Folder 55-56)
- ROTC: Science Project., 1929 (Box 31, Folder 57)
- ROTC: Science Project., 1930 (Box 31, Folder 58)
- ROTC: Science Project., 1931 (Box 31, Folder 59)
- ROTC: Science Project., 1932 (Box 31, Folder 60-62)
- ROTC: Science Project., 1933 (Box 31, Folder 63-67)
- ROTC: Science Project-Clippings., 1927-29 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- ROTC: Religion., 1929-31 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- ROTC: Factors in Student Counseling., 1929 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- ROTC: Religion in Higher Education., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
- ROTC: Religion in Higher Education., 1929 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- ROTC: Religion in Higher Education., 1931 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- ROTC: Religion in Higher Education., 1928 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- ROTC: Religion in Higher Education., 1920-34 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- ROTC: University Research Committee., 1926 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- ROTC: University Research Committee., 1927-29 (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
- ROTC: University Research Committee., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 13-18)
- ROTC: University Research Committee., 1931 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- ROTC: Athletic Association Booklets., 1916, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- ROTC: Athletics., 1920-28 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- ROTC: Graduate Manager Report., 1923-24 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- ROTC: Graduate Manager Report., 1925-26 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- ROTC: Graduate Manager Report., 1927-29 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- ROTC: Graduate Manager Report., 1930-31 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- ROTC: Graduate Manager Report., 1932-34 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- SAB Miscellaneous., 1934-37 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  Sabine, George H. Sage School of Philosophy; Sabbatic leaves.
- SAB-SAD Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  Sabine, George H. Sage School of Philosophy.
- SAD-SAG Miscellaneous., 1928-33 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  Sage, Henry M.; Gage, Simon H. Cornell University Medical College.
- SAG-SAI Miscellaneous., 1926-32 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  Sage Research Fund.
- SAIL Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  Sailer, R. W. Cornell Alumni News.
- Sackett, Henry W. (& Sackett Gorge Fund)., 1927-32 (Box 32, Folder 32-35)
  Sackett, Sarah; Treman, Robert H. Sage Research Fund; Cascadilla Glen.
- SAINT Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- SAINT-SAL Miscellaneous., 1926-34 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  Weigle, W. Harold.
- SAL-SALM Miscellaneous. Sale, William M. Salaries., 1923-31 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- SALM-SALZ Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  Wadsworth, James W.; Salmon, Thomas W.
- SAM-SAMP Miscellaneous., 1928-36 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  Sampson, Martin W.; Sailer, R. W.
- SAMP-SAN Miscellaneous., 1924-29 (Box 32, Folder 41-42)
  Sampson, Martin W. Dept. of English.
- SAN Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 32, Folder 43-46)
  Sanderson, Dwight; Sanderson, E. N. Dept. of Rural Social Organization; Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Company.
- SANF-SAP Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  Sanger, Margaret; Santayana, George.
- SAR-SAU Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  Sargent, Porter.
- SAU-SAW Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 32, Folder 49)
- SAV Miscellaneous., 1926-33 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  Savage, Maxwell.
- SAV-SCAN Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  Sawyer, Philip.
- SCAN-SCH Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 32, Folder 52)
- SCHIFF Miscellaneous., 1912-31 (Box 32, Folder 53-54)
- Schiff Foundation., 1922-26 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- SCHL-SCHM Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  Schling, Max; Schmidt, Nathaniel.
- SCHM Miscellaneous., 1923-24 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  Schmidt, Nathaniel; Hughes, Charles E.; Schmidt, Friedrich. Institute of International Education.
- SCHM-SCHO Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  Schoellkopf, J. F.
- SCHO-SCHOL Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  Schoellkopf, J. F.; Schoellkopf, Paul A.
- SCHOL-SCHOT Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  Schuchardt, William H.
- SCHR-SCHU Miscellaneous., 1925-29 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- SCHU-SCHUR Miscellaneous., 1930-36 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  Schurman, Jacob Gould.
- Schurman Miscellaneous., 1928-31 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- SCHUR-SCHW Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  Schurman, Jacob Gould; Schwab, Charles M. Schiff Foundation.
- SCI Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- SCI-SCO Miscellaneous., 1923-30 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  Scolten, Adrian.
- SCO Miscellaneous., 1933-37 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  Merritt, Ernest; Scott, E. H.; Bostwick, William.
- SCO-SCU Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  Scott, Walter Dill.
- Seaman, Major Louis Livingston., 1925-26 (Box 33, Folder 15-19)
- SEA-SEAR Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  Fulton, Creed W. Seal and Serpent.
- SEAR-SEC Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  Sebring, Edgar D.
- SEC-SEE Miscellaneous., 1916-29 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- SEE-SEI Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  Seligman, Edwin R. A.
- SEL-SELV Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- SEM-SEN Miscellaneous. Senior, John L.; Gugler, Eric., 1922-35 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- SEN-SER Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  Senior, John L.; Serviss, Garret P.
- SES-SF Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- SHA Miscellaneous., 1924-32 (Box 33, Folder 28-31)
  Shapley, Harlow; Shaw, Charles Gray. Shanghai American School; National Housing Committee.
- SHE-SHEL Miscellaneous., 1927-36 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  Sheldon, Edward W. Frasch Foundation.
- SHEL-SHEP Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  Shepard, C. Sidney.
- SHEP-SHER Miscellaneous. Shepard, C. Sidney. Smith College., 1922-31 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- SHER-SHIP Miscellaneous., 1923-30 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- SHIP-SHOR Miscellaneous., 1926-32 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  Shoemaker, Marshall N.
- SHOR-SHR Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  Shreve, R. H. College of Architecture.
- SHR-SHU Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  Shreve, R. H.
- SIA-SIB Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  Sibley, Harper; Sibley, R. P. Siam.
- Sibley, R. P., 1922-37 (Box 33, Folder 40-49)
  College of Arts and Sciences; University Faculty.
- SIC-SIG Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  Quigley, George E.; Ludlow, Chester W. Sigma Xi.
- SIG-SIM Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  Wright, Albert Hazen; Simkhovitch, Vladimir G. Sigma Xi.
- SIM-SIMP Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  Simons, L. R. New York State College of Agriculture Extension Services.
- SIMP Miscellaneous., 1923-31 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  Simpson, Smith; Simpson, Sutherland. Carnegie Foundation.
- SIMS-SIV Miscellaneous., 1926-31 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  Sinclair, Upton.
- SIV-SKI Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  Skewes, Oswald. Skidmore College.
- SKI-SLA Miscellaneous., 1927-34 (Box 33, Folder 56)
- SLA Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  Slichter, Sumner H.; Sloan, George A.
- SLO-SLY Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  Sloan, George A.
- Simmons, L. N., 1933-37 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  Board of Trustees; Office of the Comptroller.
- Simmons, L. N., 1923-32 (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
- SMA-Smiley Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  Smart, Harold R.; Roosevelt, Eleanor.
- Smiley, D. F., 1924-34 (Box 34, Folder 5-8)
  Dept. of Hygiene and Preventive Medicine.
- Smith, A Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  Smith, Albert W. Chimes.
- Smith A-C Miscellaneous., 1921-3 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  Smith, Albert W.; Smith, Bryant. Chimes.
- Smith C-G Miscellaneous., 1931-35 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  Smith, Carolyn Scofield.
- Smith, Goldwin., 1924 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Smith, Goldwin - Lecture Series., 1924-33 (Box 34, Folder 13-21)
- Smith, H Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  Smith, Howard C.; Smith, Harold D. Sage Chapel.
- Smith, H-L Miscellaneous., 1924-32 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  Smith, Harold D.; Smith, H. W.; Carman, Alice B.; Smith, Louis P. Sage Chapel.
- Smith, L-O Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  Smith, Louis P.; Smith, O. W.
- Smith, O Miscellaneous., 1932-35 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  Smith, 0. W.
- Smith, O-P Miscellaneous., 1913-33 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  Smith, Preserved.
- Smith, P-SMITHS Miscellaneous., 1921-28 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- SMO-SNO Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  Snavely, Carl.
- SNO-SNY Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  Snyder, Herbert; Snyder, Virgil.
- SNY-SOB Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  Snyder, Virgil. American Mathematical Society.
- SOB-SOC Miscellaneous., 1926-37 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  Society for the Preservation of American Principles; Inter-Fraternity Council; Student Council.
- Society Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 34, Folder 32-36)
  Nourse, E. G. Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences; Social Science Research Council; New York State Dept. of Social Welfare; Society for the Promotion of Engineering Education.
- SOC-Soil Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Soil-SOP Miscellaneous., 1929-37 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  Sommer, Roy F.
- SOP-SOUTH Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  Southard, Frank A.
- SOUTH-Southern Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  University of South Dakota.
- Southern Miscellaneous., 1928-30 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  Bancroft, Wilder D. University of Southern California.
- Southern-SOW Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  Borden, Albert G.
- SPA-SPAR Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  Borden, Albert G. Spain.
- SPAR-SPER Miscellaneous., 1926-35 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- SPER-SPOL Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  Sperry, Willard L.
- SPOR-SPRI Miscellaneous., 1925-33 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  Berry, Romeyn; Spring, Samuel N. Dept. of Forestry.
- SPRI-SPRO Miscellaneous., 1923-29 (Box 34, Folder 47)
- STA-STAF Miscellaneous., 1924-31 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  Stable Money Association.
- STAF-STAL Miscellaneous., 1925-34 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  Stalker, Gale H.
- STALL-STAN Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  Stambaugh, John; Penhale, Clayton A.; Taylor, Myron C. Cornell College; Standard Statistics Company.
- STAN Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  Jordan, David Starr; Stang, Fredrik. Stanford University.
- STAP-STAR Miscellaneous. Stark, Malcolm., 1923-37 (Box 34, Folder 52)
- STAT- (Statler) STATE Miscellaneous., 1927-33 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  Letchworth, Edward H. Dept. of Hotel Administration; Statler Foundation.